Inventory of the American National Red Cross records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Commission for Siberia, 1918-1920
  - Miscellaneous documents of the Siberian Commission, 1918-1920
    - Vladivostok, 1919-1920
      - Mayor, 1920
        Box/Folder 173: 23
      - Port of Vladivostok, map, undated
        Box/Folder 173: 24
      - Resolution of the Town Hall Duma, 1920
        Box/Folder 173: 25
      - Revolution attempted, November 1919.
        Box/Folder 173: 26. Includes report by Riley H. Allen, 1920
      - YMCA, relief work, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 173: 27
      - Enisei County relief expedition, 1919
        Box/Folder 173: 28
    - Zemstvo (president A. Medvedev), 1918-1920.
      - General, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 173: 29
      - Achinsk, 1919
        Box/Folder 173: 30
      - Eastern Department of the All-Russian Zemstvo Union, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 173: 31
      - Siberian branches, 1918-1920
        Box/Folder 174: 1
      - Siberian Cooperative Union, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 174: 2
      - Vladivostok area, 1919-1920 (Reel 257)
        Box/Folder 174: 3-4
    - Unidentified excerpt of report, undated
      Box/Folder 174: 5
- Commission for Southern Russia, 1919-1922
  - Ukraine, 1919-1922
    - Reports, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 174: 6
    - Supplies, 1920
      Box/Folder 174: 7
    - Correspondence, 1919-1921
      Box/Folder 174: 8
    - Confidential file, 1919
      Box/Folder 174: 9
  - Liquidation supplies, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 174: 10
  - Kuban' Unit, 1919
    Box/Folder 174: 11
  - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 12
  - Letters of appreciation, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 174: 13
  - American Mennonite Relief Mission, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 174: 14
  - Budget and appropriations, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 15
  - Child welfare, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 174: 16
  - Medical work, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 17
  - Finances, 1920 (Reel 258)
    Box/Folder 174: 18-20
  - Couriers service, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 21
  - Civilian relief, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 174: 22-23
  - Personnel, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 24
  - Appeals, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 174: 25-26
  - Memorandum on conference regarding South Russia, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 27
  - Russian Relief and Reconstruction Fund, London, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 28
  - Military relief, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 29
  - Refugees in Crimea, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 30
  - Program, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 174: 31-32
  - Publicity, 1920
    Box/Folder 174: 33
  - Reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 175: 1-8
  - Reports, 1920-1921 (Reel 259)
    Box/Folder 175: 9-10
  - Supplies, 1920
    Box/Folder 175: 11-12
  - Transportation, 1920
    Box/Folder 175: 13
  - The Union of Russian Towns, Constantinople, 1921
    Box/Folder 175: 14-15
  - "Medical and Sanitary Organizations and Institutions of the Crimea", by Dr. N. Dolgopoloff, report, 1921
    Box/Folder 175: 16
  - "Report on the Medical and Sanitary Conditions of Life in the Crimea at the End of the Year 1920", by Dr. N. Dolgopoloff
    Box/Folder 175: 17
  - Supplies delivered to Russian Red Cross, Galatz, for use by General Denikin's Army, 1919
    Box/Folder 175: 18-19
  - Confidential file, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 175: 20
  - Miscellany, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 175: 21
- Commission for Western Russia and Baltic States, 1917-1922
  - Official communications, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 175: 22-23
  - Official communications, 1919-1922 (Reel 260)
    Box/Folder 176: 1-5
  - Telegram book, 1920
    Box/Folder 176: 6-10
  - General orders, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 176: 11
  - American Relief Administration, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 176: 12-14
  - The Red Cross Bulletin, Riga, 1920-1921 (Reel 261)
    Box/Folder 176: 15-16
  - Records of supplies shipped on the SS Hansa from Commission to Western Russia and Baltic States to Brest, France, 18 October 1920
    Box/Folder 176: 17-18
  - Report on supply accounting, 1921
    Box/Folder 176: 19
  - Distribution supplies, reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 176: 20
  - Transportation, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 176: 21
  - Senator Joseph I., France, 1921
    Box/Folder 176: 22
  - Liquidation, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 176: 23
  - Home service, 1920
    Box/Folder 176: 24
  - Official communications, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 177: 1-3
  - Official communications, 1920-1921 (Reel 262)
    Box/Folder 177: 4-6
  - The Red Cross Bulletin, Riga, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 177: 7-8
  - Ambulances-hospitals, reports, 1917
    Box/Folder 177: 9-10
  - Appeals, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 177: 11-14
  - Appeals, 1920-1922 (Reel 263)
    Box/Folder 177: 15
  - Budget and appropriation, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 177: 16
  - Child health, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 177: 17
  - Child welfare, 1917
    Box/Folder 177: 18
  - Civilian relief, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 177: 19-21
  - Confidential file, 1921
    Box/Folder 178: 1-3
  - American Embassy, Petrograd, 1917
    Box/Folder 178: 4
  - Letters of appreciation, 1920-1922 (Reel 264)
    Box/Folder 178: 5-8
  - Estonia, reports of activities, 1920-1922
    - General, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 178: 9-10
    - Finances, 1921
      Box/Folder 178: 11
    - Dorpat, 1920
      Box/Folder 178: 12
    - Reval, 1920
      Box/Folder 178: 13-14
    - Walk, 1920
      Box/Folder 178: 15
  - Finland, 1918-1921
    - Correspondence, 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 178: 16
    - Official communications, reports, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 178: 17-20
    - "The Help of ARC to Russian Refugees in Finland", report by Russian Red Cross representative in Finland Professor Zeidler, and other documents, 1920-1921 (Reel 265)
      Box/Folder 178: 21
  - Latvia, 1919-1922
    - Reports, 1919-1922
      Box/Folder 178: 22-24
    - Anti-Bolshevik movement, Kronshtadt, 1921
      Box/Folder 178: 25
    - Mitau district, reports, 1920
      Box/Folder 178: 26
    - "Report on Conditions in Latgalia", by Lt. Dale Houghton, 1920
      Box/Folder 179: 1
    - "Report of Activities in Latvia", by Major L.G. Patterson, ARC, Bureau of Requirements, 13 December 1919
      Box/Folder 179: 2
    - Transportation Department, 1921
      Box/Folder 179: 3
    - Reschitza District, reports, 1920
      Box/Folder 179: 4
    - Lady Muriel Paget's Mission to Eastern Europe, 1921
      Box/Folder 179: 5
    - Personnel, 1921
      Box/Folder 179: 6
  - Lithuania, 1919-1921
    - Civilian relief, reports, 1919-1921
      Box/Folder 179: 7-11
    - Letter books, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 179: 12-13
    - Letter books, 1919-1920 (Reel 266)
      Box/Folder 179: 14-15
    - Program, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 179: 16-20
    - Reports, 1919-1922
      Box/Folder 179: 21-25
    - Reports, 1919-1922 (Reel 267)
      Box/Folder 180: 1-7
    - Publicity, 1921-1922
      Box/Folder 180: 8
    - Public health, undated
      Box/Folder 180: 9
    - Medical work, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 180: 10
    - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1919-1921
      Box/Folder 180: 11
    - Military relief, 1920
      Box/Folder 180: 12
    - Personnel, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 180: 13-14
    - Miscellany, correspondence, reports, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 180: 15
    - Miscellany, correspondence, reports, 1920-1922 (Reel 268)
      Box/Folder 180: 16
- Commission for Russia, 1917-1922
  - Russian Red Cross Society, 1917-1921
    - Personnel, references, introductions, business cards, 1917-1918
      Box/Folder 180: 17-18
    - Correspondence, reports, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 180: 19-22
    - Correspondence, reports, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 181: 1-2
  - Russian prisoners and refugees of war, 1919-1922
    Box/Folder 181: 3-4
  - Relief of allied prisoners in Petrograd and Moscow, 1917-1919 (Reel 269)
    Box/Folder 181: 5-6
  - Sanitation, reports, 1917
    Box/Folder 181: 7
  - Sale of ARC supplies by Lithuania, 1920
    Box/Folder 181: 8
  - Reports of activities, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 181: 9-13
  - Mission to Russia, reports, correspondence, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 181: 14-16
  - Food and clothing supplies, 1917
    Box/Folder 181: 17-19
  - Finances, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 181: 20
  - General file, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 181: 21
  - Before Peace and After (A Scheme for the Provision of Technical Assistance in Russia), by the Secretary of Education Department L. Gatz, 1917
    Box/Folder 181: 22
  - American prisoners and refugees of war, 1920-1922 (Reel 270)
    Box/Folder 182: 1-3
  - Civilian relief, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 182: 4-5
  - Famine relief, 1921
    Box/Folder 182: 6
  - Appeals, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 182: 7-8
  - Program, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 182: 9-11
  - Care and relief of Russian prisoners of war in Germany, 1919 (Reel 271)
    Box/Folder 182: 12
  - Russian Red Cross Society--Russian ouvroir at Nice for prisoners of war, 1919-1922
    - Countess O. Bobrinsky, Paris, 1920
      Box/Folder 182: 13
    - Princess Shakhovsky, Versailles, 1920
      Box/Folder 182: 14
    - Marie Maklakoff, Russian Embassy, Paris, 1919 1920
      Box/Folder 182: 15
    - Madame la Baronne Proctor, Paris, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 182: 16
    - Russian Imperial Guard Lieut. Colonel Mestcherinoff, 1919
      Box/Folder 182: 17
    - President of Central Committee for Russian Relief, L. Lubimoff, Paris, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 182: 18-19
- Commission for Western Russia and Baltic States, 1917-1922
  - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1920-1922
    - General, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 182: 20
    - Austrian, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 182: 21
    - German, 1920
      Box/Folder 182: 22
    - Hungarian, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 182: 23
    - Repatriation, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 183: 1-8
    - Repatriation, 1920-1921 (Reel 272)
      Box/Folder 183: 9-10
- Commission to Switzerland, 1917-1921
  - Report of the Department of Civilian Relief, December 31, 1918
    Box/Folder 183: 11
  - Reports of activities, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 183: 12-16
  - Donation to Swiss Government for influenza epidemic, 1919
    Box/Folder 183: 17
  - XXIIIe rapport sur la Croix-Rouge suisse pour l'année 1917, Swiss Red Cross, Bern, 1918
    Box/Folder 183: 18
  - Major Carl Taylor, ARC, reports, Bern, 1918
    Box/Folder 183: 19
  - Civilian relief, Serbian officers and students, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 184: 1-2
  - Uniform for Swiss personnel, 1918-1919 (Reel 273)
    Box/Folder 184: 3
  - Reports, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 184: 4-10
  - Refugees, diseased, 1919
    Box/Folder 184: 11
  - Statistical questionnaire to ARC Commission, 1919
    Box/Folder 184: 12
  - St. Gall branch, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 184: 13-14
  - Supplies and office matters, Berne, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 184: 15
  - Scrapbook, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 184: 16
- Washington Headquarters, 1917-1921
  - Chairman of the War Council of the ARC Henry P.S. Davison, statements on arriving from Europe, circa 1918
    Box/Folder 184: 17
  - Appointment of Mrs. Herbert Hoover as Associate Director, Bureau of Canteen Service, 1 October 1918
    Box/Folder 184: 18
  - List of camps to be abandoned, Bureau of Transportation, 1919
    Box/Folder 184: 19
  - Bureau of Prisoner Relief, 1917 (Reel 274)
    Box/Folder 184: 20-21
  - Interned Americans, list, 1917
    Box/Folder 184: 22
  - Commission for Relief in the Near East, 1919
    Box/Folder 184: 23-24
  - Commission for Switzerland, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 184: 25
  - Commission for Switzerland, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 185: 1-2
  - Acte de Constitution de la Croix-Rouge Américaine et Actes d'Amendements, 1918
    Box/Folder 185: 3
  - Conference of the Publicity Men for the Fourteen Divisions of the ARC, Washington, D.C., 23 July 1918
    Box/Folder 185: 4-5
  - American Committee for Armenian and Syrian Relief, 1916-1917
    Box/Folder 185: 6-8
  - American Red Cross Bulletin, Washington, D.C., 1917-1921 (Reel 275)
    Box/Folder 185: 9-12
  - Department of Foreign Relief, diagram book, 1918
    Box/Folder 185: 13-14
  - Printed forms from all departments and bureaus for the Red Cross library and museum, 1918
    - Bureau of personnel
      Box/Folder 185: 15
    - Organization table and charts
      Box/Folder 185: 16
    - Office supplies
      Box/Folder 185: 17
    - Purchasing
      Box/Folder 185: 18
    - Civil affairs (Reel 276)
      Box/Folder 185: 19
    - Warehouse
      Box/Folder 185: 20
    - Home service
      Box/Folder 186: 1
  - Special Committee to Survey ARC work since March 1919, Washington, D.C., 20 October 1920
    Box/Folder 186: 2-4
  - Pacific Division--Shipping situation, San Francisco, 1919
    Box/Folder 186: 5
  - Bureau of Transportation, statistics statements showing foodstuff exported to all foreign countries, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 186: 6-8
  - Department of Foreign Relief, instructions, 1918
    Box/Folder 186: 9
  - Department of Foreign Relief, instructions, 1918 (Reel 277)
    Box/Folder 186: 10-11
  - New York American, articles, July 1921
    Box/Folder 186: 12-13
- Paris Headquarters, 1918-1922
  - Commission for Europe, 1918-1921
    - Letters of appreciation, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 186: 14
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1918-1921
      Box/Folder 186: 15-17
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1918-1921 (Reel 278)
      Box/Folder 187: 1-2
    - Friends War Victims Relief Committee, 1918
      Box/Folder 187: 3
    - Spanish flu epidemic--Camps in Germany, 1918
      Box/Folder 187: 4
    - Rules and regulations, status, 1918-1920.
      Box/Folder 187: 5-7. Includes Geneva Convention to ameliorate the condition of wounded militaries of armies in the field, August 22, 1864
    - Airplane service, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 187: 8
  - Commission for Relief in the Near East, 1919
    Box/Folder 187: 9-10
  - American Library Association, Library War Service, 1919
    Box/Folder 187: 11-12
  - American Relief Administration, correspondence, reports, 1918-1922
    Box/Folder 187: 13-18
  - American Relief Administration, correspondence, reports, 1918-1922 (Reel 279)
    Box/Folder 187: 19- 25
  - American Relief Administration, correspondence, reports, 1918-1922
    Box/Folder 188: 1-4
  - Commission for Europe, 1918-1922
    - Appeals, 1919-1922
      Box/Folder 188: 5-8
    - Appeals, 1919-1922 (Reel 280)
      Box/Folder 188: 9-12
    - Reports, 1920
      Box/Folder 188: 13-17
    - Appropriations, 1919-1922 (Reel 281)
      Box/Folder 188: 18-21
    - Appropriations, 1919-1921
      Box/Folder 189: 1-4
    - Army relations, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 189: 5
    - Barracks (portable houses), 1919
      Box/Folder 189: 6
    - Liquidation of automobile supplies and equipment by the Liquidation Committee, report, 1919-1922
      Box/Folder 189: 7-8
    - Budgets, 1919-1922
      Box/Folder 189: 9-12
    - Budgets, 1919-1922 (Reel 282)
      Box/Folder 189: 13-16
    - Cable Bureau, 1919-1922
      Box/Folder 189: 17-20
    - Chapters, 1919-1922
      Box/Folder 189: 21-22
    - Cannes, France, reports, 1918 (Reel 283)
      Box/Folder 190: 1
    - Netherlands Chapter, 1920
      Box/Folder 190: 2
    - Child health, 1919-1922
    - Reports, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 190: 3-10
    - Reports, 1920-1922 (Reel 284)
      Box/Folder 190: 11-13
    - Chaperonage of children, 1919
      Box/Folder 190: 14
    - Exhibit, 1921-1922
      Box/Folder 190: 15-21
    - Instructions, 1921-1922
      Box/Folder 191: 1
    - Sanitary train, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 191: 2-3
    - Executive circular letters, 1921-1922
      Box/Folder 191: 4
    - Circular letters, 1921-1922
      Box/Folder 191: 5-6
    - Civilian relief, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 191: 7-8
    - Old clothing campaign, 1919-1920 (Reel 285)
      Box/Folder 191: 9-11
    - Commissary, 1919
      Box/Folder 191: 12
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 191: 13
    - Conferences, 1919-1922
    - Florence, 1919
      Box/Folder 191: 14
    - Geneva, 1917-1919
      Box/Folder 191: 15-16
    - Venice, 1920
      Box/Folder 191: 17
    - Medical directors, 1922
      Box/Folder 191: 18-19
    - American Legation, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1919
      Box/Folder 191: 20-25
    - American Legation, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1919
      Box/Folder 192: 1-2
    - American Legation, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1919 (Reel 286)
      Box/Folder 192: 3-6
    - Courier service, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 192: 7-9
    - Donations to and from ARC, 1920-1922 (Reel 287)
      Box/Folder 192: 10-18
    - Donations from ARC, 1920-1922 (Reel 288)
      Box/Folder 193: 1-6
    - Decorations, medals to and from ARC, 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 193: 7-8
    - "Europe's Need," report by Henry P. Davison, craftsman of the Red Cross War Council during the war, 17 April 1920
      Box/Folder 193: 9
    - Exchange rates, 1920-1922 (Reel 289)
      Box/Folder 193: 10-11
    - General financial and supplies information, 31 August, 1920
      Box/Folder 193: 12
    - Reports, statistical year, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 193: 13
    - Major H.P. Seidemann, reports, 1919
      Box/Folder 193: 14
    - Inspection trips to Bucharest and Belgrade, reports by director of foreign accounts Nelson Mills, 1920
      Box/Folder 193: 15
    - All foreign sub-commissions, statistical reports, fiscal year, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 193: 16
    - Account with British Red Cross Society, report, 1920
      Box/Folder 193: 17
    - Home Service Bureau, reports, 1919-1921
      Box/Folder 193: 18-19
    - Official files, 1920
      Box/Folder 193: 20
    - Official files, 1921-1922 (Reel 290)
      Box/Folder 194: 1-3
    - Lieut. Colonel Homer Folks, reports, 1918
      Box/Folder 194: 4
    - Narrative information concerning European operations by countries, 1920
      Box/Folder 194: 5
    - Investigation of ARC by New York American, 1921
      Box/Folder 194: 6-7
    - Irish relief, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 194: 8
    - American Joint Distribution Committee, 1919-1922
      Box/Folder 194: 9-13
    - All division managers, letters, 1921
      Box/Folder 194: 14-15
    - Vice chairman letters, 1921 (Reel 291)
      Box/Folder 194: 16-17
    - Liquidation, 1919
      Box/Folder 194: 18
    - Mascots at camp Pontanezen, Brest, France, 1919
      Box/Folder 194: 19
    - Medical work, reports, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 194: 20-23
    - Medical work, reports, 1921-1922
      Box/Folder 195: 1-3
    - Miscellany correspondence, reports, and printed matter, 1920-1921
      Box/Folder 195: 4-10
    - Miscellany correspondence, reports, and printed matter, 1920-1921 (Reel 292)
      Box/Folder 195: 11-17
    - Community Motion Picture Bureau, 1919
      Box/Folder 195: 18
    - Lieut. Colonel Robert E. Olds, correspondence, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 195: 19-21
    - Official communications, 1919
      Box/Folder 195: 22
    - Permanent Blind Relief Fund for Soldiers and Sailors of the Allies, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 195: 23
    - Nurses Bureau, reports, 1919
      Box/Folder 195: 24-25
    - Office management, 1919
      Box/Folder 195: 26
    - Personnel, 1919-1920
      - General, 1919-1920 (Reel 293)
        Box/Folder 196: 1-4
      - Army, 1919
        Box/Folder 196: 5
      - Finances, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 196: 6
      - Meetings, 1919
        Box/Folder 196: 7
      - Uniforms, 1919
        Box/Folder 196: 8
      - Transportation, 1919
        Box/Folder 196: 9
      - Vacation, 1919
        Box/Folder 196: 10
    - Photography Bureau, 1919
      Box/Folder 196: 11
    - ARC policy, 1919-1920
      Box/Folder 196: 12-15
    - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1919-1921 (Reel 294)
      Box/Folder 196: 16-19
    - Program, 1919-1922
      Box/Folder 196: 20-23
    - Department of Public Information, 1918-1922
      - Reports, correspondence, 1918-1922 (Reel 295)
        Box/Folder 197: 1-7
      - Articles, 1921
        Box/Folder 197: 8
      - Weekly newsletters, 1920-1922
        Box/Folder 197: 9-10
      - Clippings of the day, 1921 (Reel 296)
        Box/Folder 197: 11-12
    - Purchases, 1919
      Box/Folder 197: 13
    - Reorganization, 1919
      Box/Folder 197: 14
    - Reports, 1919-1921
      - General, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 197: 15-19
      - General, 1920-1921
        Box/Folder 198: 1-2
      - General, 1920-1921 (Reel 297)
        Box/Folder 198: 3-7
      - Annual, 1920
        Box/Folder 198: 8
      - Material to annual report, 1920
        Box/Folder 198: 9-10
      - Finances, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 198: 11
      - Finances, 1919-1920 (Reel 298)
        Box/Folder 198: 12-15
      - Status of appropriation, 1920
        Box/Folder 198: 16
      - Narrative information concerning European operations by countries, 1920
        Box/Folder 198: 17
      - Quarterly, October-December, 1921-1922
        Box/Folder 198: 18-20
      - Annual, 1921
        Box/Folder 199: 1
      - Sales, 1919
        Box/Folder 199: 2-3
      - Sanitary train, 1920
        Box/Folder 199: 4
      - Shipments, 1919
        Box/Folder 199: 5
      - Soya beans, 1919 (Reel 299)
        Box/Folder 199: 6
      - Supplies, 1919
        - General, 1919
          Box/Folder 199: 7-8
        - List of supplies at various deports of the American Expeditionary Forces, 1919
          Box/Folder 199: 9
        - Surplus material of medical corps, index, 1919
          Box/Folder 199: 10
        - Supplies from the army, 1919
          Box/Folder 199: 11
        - Coal, 1919
          Box/Folder 199: 12
        - Supplies from France, 1919
          Box/Folder 199: 13
    - Swedish Red Cross, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 199: 14
    - Junior Red Cross, 1919-1922
      - Organization--Statement of principals, 1920-1921
        Box/Folder 199: 15
      - Reports, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 199: 16
      - Quarterly reports, 1920
        Box/Folder 199: 17
      - General correspondence, Paris-Washington, 1920-1922
        Box/Folder 199: 18-19
      - Junior Red Cross News, bulletin, 1920-1921
        Box/Folder 199: 20
      - Financial reports, 1920-1922
        Box/Folder 199: 21
    - International Red Cross Committee, 1919-1921
      - Index folder, 1920-1921
        Box/Folder 199: 22
      - American Relief Administration, 1921
        Box/Folder 199: 23
      - Conference, 10th, 1921
        Box/Folder 199: 24-25
      - Conference, 10th, 1921 (Reel 300)
        Box/Folder 200: 1-2
      - Correspondence, 1920-1921
        Box/Folder 200: 3
      - Memorandum, submitted by the Committee of Red Cross Societies, consisting of representatives of England, the United States, France, Italy, and Japan, 1919
        Box/Folder 200: 4
      - Reports, 1920-1921
        Box/Folder 200: 5
      - "La situation sanitaire en Ukraine", report by Major Ernest Léderrey, Genève, 1919-1920
        Box/Folder 200: 6
      - Bulletin International, Genève, October 1917
        Box/Folder 200: 7
      - Nouvelles de l'Agence Internationale des Prisonniers de Guerre, Genève, 1918
        Box/Folder 200: 8
      - European Relief Council, 1920
        Box/Folder 200: 9
      - Cooperation with Turkish Red Crescent Society, 1922
        Box/Folder 200: 10
      - Acting Director, Foreign Operations, Ernest P. Bicknell, 1921
        Box/Folder 200: 11
      - Chairman, ARC, Henry P. Davison, 1919
        Box/Folder 200: 12
      - Assistant to Commissioner to Europe, ARC, Curtis E. Lakeman, 1920-1921
        Box/Folder 200: 13
      - Council of the League Nations, Fridtjof Nansen, 1920
        Box/Folder 200: 14
      - Commissioner to Europe Robert E. Olds, 1920
        Box/Folder 200: 15
      - Délégué du Comité Central de la Croix-Rouge Russe pour le Secours aux Victimes de la Guerre Civile George Lodygensky, 1920
        Box/Folder 200: 16
      - Union Internationale de Secours aux Enfants, 1920-1921
        Box/Folder 200: 17
      - Save the Children Fund, 2nd International Congress, 1920-1921
        Box/Folder 200: 18
    - The History of the American National Red Cross, 1950